Gamalliel Sharon

Front-End Engineer

Creative front-end web developer who is passionate about blending the art of design with the skill of programming to design and build all aspects of the user experience and user interface. Specializes in using HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and React JS to build websites.

Bogor City, West Java, Indonesia. (+62) 877-2599-4151 sharongamalliel@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gam alliel-sharon-43ba851a4/

EXPERIENCE

Bangkit Academy — Cloud Computing Learning Path

February 2021 - June 2021

- An exclusive academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek & Traveloka. Selected as the best 3,000 among 40,000 applicants to join Bangkit Academy 2021, specifically on Cloud Computing Track.
- Learning about basic web development and Google Cloud Platform from Coursera and qwiklabs.
- Implement Google Cloud Platform on Capstone Project for "Predicting Bike Sharing Demand Based on the Previous Usage considering the Weather using Neural Network".
- Build back-end services to deploy the machine learning model into the google cloud run and build the API so the android app can interact directly with the Machine Learning Model.

Mitratel, Jakarta — Project Monitoring & Closing, Internship.

September 2020 - November 2020

- Work from home with the Project Monitoring & Closing unit team.
- Input tower tenant data from Microsoft Excel into the information system application called "M-Project".
- Separate and check all of the Minutes of handover and acceptance test reports for each tower tenant.
- Ensure that all tower tenant data are filled and correctly according to the tower tenant ID.

Bracket Studio, Jakarta — Web Developer, Internship.

June 2020 - August 2020

- Designing and developing website templates for clients by request.
- Creating company website landing page profiles based on company requests .
- As a basic web development mentor at Institut Teknologi PLN Jakarta. Teaching how to build a website from scratch using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and CSS frameworks such as Bootstrap.
- Convert UI design from Figma to HTML, CSS & JavaScript.

EDUCATION

Institut Teknologi PLN, Jakarta.

August 2017 - PRESENT

Final-year student, majoring in Informatics Engineering, Faculty of Telematika Energi with **GPA: 3.22** out of 4.00

SKILLS

Design: User Experience, Ideation and workflows, Wireframes and MockUps, Interaction and User Interface design, Prototyping.

Programming: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, MySQL.

Cloud: Google Cloud Platform

Frameworks & Libraries:Bootstrap, React JS, Material UI.

TOOLS

Figma, Git, GitHub, npm, Visual Studio Code.

INTEREST

UI Engineer, Front-End Web Development, Cloud Engineer, User Experience Design, User Interface Design.